<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<job-serve>
<row>
  <type value="Permanent" />
  <postion value="Java Developer" />
  <details value="Java/J2EE Developer - Banking - Finance - 55k-65k pa My client a global giant in the finance sector, currently has an opening in the team for a seasoned Java Developer. This is rare opportunity for the Java Developer to play a major part in the development of a Real Time trading application. The successful Java Developer will have a passion for the financial market and the use of cutting edge technology. Essential skills J2EE/J5ee development Eclipse IDE, EJB&apos;s Web Services JPA Hibernate SQL Design Patterns This is a unique opportunity for an enthusiastic Java Developer to work with a true market leader on a Greenfield project. Apply immediately to avoid disappointment! Java/J2EE Developer - Banking - Finance - 55k-65k pa" />
  <location value="London" />
  <when_start value="asap" />
  <duration value="permanent" />
  <rate value="£55 - £65" />
  <advertiser value="Explore Group (Employment Agency)" />
  <contact value="Josiah Millar" />
  <tel1 value="" />
  <tel2 value="" />
  <email value="Josiah.Millar.9BCA2.7ECA8@mail.jobserve.com" />
  <web value="" />
  <reference value="JS" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/E3373BCAA5919AC43.jsap" />
  <visa value="" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:06" />
</row>
<row>
  <type value="Contract" />
  <postion value="PMO Analyst" />
  <details value="PMO Analyst/My client a leading Insurance organisation require a contract pmo analyst to work on their Solvency II Project. To effectively undertake the monitoring, control and reporting of the Solvency II project for Risk Programme Management ensuring adherence and compliance with all corporate governance requirements. Key Skills: Corporate, Industry and Professional Governance - able to become quickly proficient in required standards. Project/Programme Management - Proficient in principles, methods, techniques and tools for the effective project office management of a project through to the successful achievement of project objectives. Business proposals and budgets - Proficient in tools for preparing and monitoring business cases and expenditure against plans. Configuration management - expert in the control and management of project products (or configuration items) including documentation, services, suppliers by the use and application of strict change management, recording and version control. Software skills - Excel, word, Powerpoint and MSP. Excellent market rates. Please contact Darrin Mathie at Eames IT with CV&apos;s in the first instance." />
  <location value="South East England" />
  <when_start value="ASAP" />
  <duration value="6 month rolling" />
  <rate value="Negotiable" />
  <advertiser value="Eames Consulting Group Ltd (Employment Business)" />
  <contact value="Darrin Mathie" />
  <tel1 value="0207 092 3217" />
  <tel2 value="0207 092 3201" />
  <email value="Darrin.Mathie.73817.C6604@mail.jobserve.com" />
  <web value="" />
  <reference value="JS-IT/DM/PMOA" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/E55C13250AF9B82AB.jsap" />
  <visa value="" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:10" />
</row>
<row>
  <type value="Contract" />
  <postion value="Business Analyst (London Market)" />
  <details value="Business Analyst required for my client, a leading London Market Insurance organisation on a 6 months contract. My client requires an experienced Business Analyst who will be responsible for the delivery of new and/or, enhanced high quality systems and processes that benefit the business and be pro-active in recommending solutions that challenge current business practice to ensure delivery of a more efficient business process. You will have an up to date appreciation of the technical requirements ie SQL Server, Process Analysis, Data Modelling, Function Design coupled with; current knowledge management and problem tracking tools, and documentation aids such as UML and Visio. You will also require first class report writing skills and have considerable expertise in dealing with and managing 3rd party vendors. This is an excellent opportunity to join a forward thinking and market leading organisation and this role would ideally suit candidates with excellent attention to detail. Please send CV&apos;s to Darrin Mathie at Eames Consulting to register your interest." />
  <location value="City Of London" />
  <when_start value="ASAP" />
  <duration value="6 months" />
  <rate value="Negotiable" />
  <advertiser value="Eames Consulting Group Ltd (Employment Business)" />
  <contact value="Darrin Mathie" />
  <tel1 value="0207 092 3217" />
  <tel2 value="0207 092 3201" />
  <email value="Darrin.Mathie.C283B.7DC41@mail.jobserve.com" />
  <web value="" />
  <reference value="JS-IT/DM/BA" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/E5A6AE9AFE070094C.jsap" />
  <visa value="" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:12" />
</row>
<row>
  <type value="Permanent" />
  <postion value="Business Analyst (Insurance)" />
  <details value="Business Analyst for a leading Insurance organisation. My client requires an experienced Business Analyst who will be responsible for the delivery of new and/or, enhanced high quality systems and processes that benefit the business and be pro-active in recommending solutions that challenge current business practice to ensure delivery of a more efficient business process. You will have an up to date appreciation of the technical requirements ie SQL Server, Process Analysis, Data Modelling, Function Design coupled with; current knowledge management and problem tracking tools, and documentation aids such as UML and Visio. You will also require first class report writing skills. This is an excellent opportunity to join a forward thinking and market leading organisation and this role would ideally suit candidates with an excellent attention to detail. Please send CV&apos;s to Darrin Mathie at Eames Consulting to register your interest." />
  <location value="Suffolk" />
  <when_start value="ASAP" />
  <duration value="" />
  <rate value="£45k - £55k per annum + benefits" />
  <advertiser value="Eames Consulting Group Ltd (Employment Agency)" />
  <contact value="Darrin Mathie" />
  <tel1 value="0207 092 3217" />
  <tel2 value="0207 092 3201" />
  <email value="Darrin.Mathie.2DF3B.3D9E6@mail.jobserve.com" />
  <web value="" />
  <reference value="JS-IT/DM/10307" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/E26C14124ACEBA137.jsap" />
  <visa value="" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:12" />
</row>
<row>
  <type value="Permanent" />
  <postion value="Yellsites Designer" />
  <details value="We are currently looking for a number of designers to work on our leading new plus or premium website products. You will work with the dedicated Web Account Manager and use our bespoke UX tools to deliver high quality online designs. You will have the ability to understand client briefs and identify innovative solutions that fulfill those in a professional and timely manner. These roles will be for Yell Adworks. KEY ACCOUNTABILITIES: * Delivery of high quality websites for our customers * Portray a professional and responsive service to our key customers * Provide quality design and ideas that exceed customer expectations and which will deliver high traffic for their business KEY KNOWLEDGE AND EXPERIENCE: * Advanced knowledge and experience of Photoshop * Ability to think conceptually and generate ideas * Ability to create designs which clearly deliver on business objectives * Strong photography and typography knowledge * Ability to rationalise and communicate design decisions and principles in a client-facing environment * Knowledge of SEO best practices ADDITIONAL KEY SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE: * Keen eye for detail * Flexible approach * Strong interpersonal skills * Can work on their own and as part of a large team This role would be suitable for a recent university graduate who has studied a relevant design course." />
  <location value="Glasgow" />
  <when_start value="" />
  <duration value="" />
  <rate value="£19k - £23k per annum + Salary + benefits" />
  <advertiser value="YELL (Company)" />
  <contact value="Yell National Resourcing Team" />
  <tel1 value="7739047762" />
  <tel2 value="" />
  <email value="" />
  <web value="" />
  <reference value="JS-.00680" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/E4258699D88A279DE.jsap" />
  <visa value="Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:14" />
</row>
<row>
  <type value="Contract" />
  <postion value="SAP MM consultant- English" />
  <details value="SAP MM consultant- France - Contract SAP MM consultant- France - English &amp; French Amoria Bond are looking for a SAP MM for our client based in France in an ideal location. The successful SAP MM ( Material Management) consultant will need to have a strong experience in this manufacturing. You will be responsible for the conception, the process, the establishment of a model in SAP and the stocks. As an excellent SAP MM consultant, you will have the excellent opportunity to work within an international project. You will need to have of good knowledge of French both verbal and written. It would be appreciable to have knowledge of Russian or to have knowledge of this environment. In order to be successful in this project, you will also need to: * have excellent knowledge in SAP MM * have done at least 2 implementation project ( Full life cycle) * have strong functional knowledge with good technical knowledge * have a strong logistics manufacturing and production experience * have worked on integration with Finance modules * have worked a strong experience with importation of flow * it would be appreciated to have experience in discrete manufacturing The successful SAP MM consultant will have the opportunity to work within a multicultural English environment in France for our client as well as having. * An excellent contract opportunity in an ideal location in France *Possibility to have your contract renewed according to your performance within the project * Swift application" />
  <location value="France" />
  <when_start value="" />
  <duration value="53 weeks" />
  <rate value="Negotiable" />
  <advertiser value="Amoria Bond Ltd (Employment Business)" />
  <contact value="Magali Toussaint" />
  <tel1 value="+31 (0) 20 80 80 888" />
  <tel2 value="0845 280 0090" />
  <email value="Magali.Toussaint.3BF35.7C790@mail.jobserve.com" />
  <web value="http://www.amoriabond.com" />
  <reference value="JS-J8482" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/EEFB9E8509543B0C4.jsap" />
  <visa value="Applications considered from candidates who require a Work Visa" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:26" />
</row>
<row>
  <type value="Permanent" />
  <postion value="Test Manager - Insurance" />
  <details value="Test Manager, our client, a leading risk management adviser and insurance and reinsurance broker, is looking to recruit a Test Manager to support a major transformation programme currently underway in the London Market. The role will include managing the Acceptance Process in each stage of the testing lifecycle, eg UAT, Systems Testing, etc. Responsibilities will include development of relevant test strategies, test plans from functional requirements and test scripts. You will be required to manage and coordinate each stage of the systems testing cycle by working closely with Business Project managers and end business users. You will have 3 years Test Management and at least 5 years general IT or systems experience. You will require a strong appreciation of the Business Analysis process, be well organised and have good inter-personnel skills. Experience of the Insurance Industry would be an advantage This is an excellent opportunity within a large company offering excellent salary and benefits. Please email your CV including current package details" />
  <location value="London" />
  <when_start value="ASAP" />
  <duration value="" />
  <rate value="£45k plus benefits" />
  <advertiser value="Stirling Consultancy (Company)" />
  <contact value="Resourcing Department" />
  <tel1 value="" />
  <tel2 value="" />
  <email value="Resourcing.Department.291BE.F0152@mail.jobserve.com" />
  <web value="" />
  <reference value="JS-ACB-101025-1" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/E674BC8222D11A076.jsap" />
  <visa value="Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:26" />
</row>
<row>
  <type value="Contract" />
  <postion value="Oracle Hyperion Strategic Finance Management Consultant" />
  <details value="We are currently looking for a high-calibred Hyperion Functional Consultant with experience and track record from the SFM module with respect to design, configuration, testing and implementation. --- Apply now for one of the most exciting Corporate Finance Programmes in London in 2011/2012 --- Mandatory Requirements Investment Banking, Banking or Large-Scale Finance Experience Implementation experience Hyperion experience with focus on SFM The consultant will take part in a long term programme and have significant scope for career progression and group level finance in one of the world&apos;s largest financial institutions. Job Description Provide process, operating model, or systems design and support for designated applications and business functions for development activities. Example Activities: Support a particular functional or system aspect of a project through implementation Facilitate requirements gathering Create conceptual and configuration designs that support the business requirements Identify system issues/risks, articulate to management, help resolve Conduct peer reviews Produce process architecture that define all processes and their relationships with the business architecture and/or the details of specific processes within the process architecture Leverage application knowledge with custom development skills to design reports, interfaces, conversions, software extensions and forms Work with the application team to resolve any issues that arise out of the testing" />
  <location value="London" />
  <when_start value="Immediate" />
  <duration value="6 months + extensions" />
  <rate value="250 - 600 day" />
  <advertiser value="G X Consult. Ltd (Company)" />
  <contact value="Contact Services" />
  <tel1 value="" />
  <tel2 value="" />
  <email value="Contact.Services.FB8FF.D2998@mail.jobserve.com" />
  <web value="" />
  <reference value="JS TPP22" />
  <job_url value="http://www.jobserve.com/E80B47BD9AA5EDB14.jsap" />
  <visa value="Applications welcome from candidates who require a Work Visa" />
  <date value="25/10/10 20:34" />
</row>
</job-serve>

